Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
Gregg Smith Singers Recordings
- Recordings
  - RozRem (1), gss_857; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is could be a recording of Rosalind Rees Sings Ned Rorem – with the composer at the piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Rozrem (2), 03/18/1983; gss_849; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is could be a recording of Rosalind Rees Sings Ned Rorem – with the composer at the piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - RozRem (2), 03/25/1983; gss_856; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is could be a recording of Rosalind Rees Sings Ned Rorem – with the composer at the piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - RozRem (2), gss_858; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is could be a recording of Rosalind Rees Sings Ned Rorem – with the composer at the piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Rozrem (3), gss_850; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is could be a recording of Rosalind Rees Sings Ned Rorem – with the composer at the piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - RozRem (4), gss_860; Based on the GSS discography on their website, this is could be a recording of Rosalind Rees Sings Ned Rorem – with the composer at the piano.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - St. John Passion, gss_922; Most likely this is "St. John Passion" a sacred oratorio by Johann Sebastian Bach.; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Oversize 61)
  - St. John Passion (conclusion); Aesop's Fables, gss_923; Most likely this is a recording of "St. John Passion" a sacred oratorio by Johann Sebastian Bach and "Aesop's Fables" opera by Gregg Smith.; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Oversize 61)
  - St. Paul's (2), gss_879; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Sandburg: Always; Poems (14); Smith; [William] Mayer: Eve of St. Agnes, gss_107; Illegible notes about the content are written on the box. Mar 21 [no year]; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - Saranac 39-40 (14), gss_833; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Saranac reels 1-3 (1), gss_900; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
    1 - [Wallingford] Riegger: "Who Can Revoke"; 2 - [Carolyn L.] Madison: "Bitte"; [Paul] Chihara: "Lie Lightly Gentle Earth"
  - Saranac reels 4-6 (2), Choral New Yorker, gss_864; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    "Caroline Million"
  - Saranac reels 7-9 (3), Choral New Yorker (con't), gss_865; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    Hen Party; [George] Gershwin: "Jolly Tar" (preliminary take); Michael Hennagin: "House on the Hill" (solos only)
  - Saranac reels 10-12 (4), gss_866; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    Michael Hennagin: "House on the Hill" (solos con't); [George] Gershwin: "Jolly Tar"; "Spring is come" (fine design solos)
  - Saranac reels 13-15 (5), gss_867; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    Michael Hennagin: "House on the Hill"
  - Saranac reels 16-18 (6), gss_868; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    Musicians: Prelude
  - Saranac reels 19-21 (7), gss_869; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    Musicians: Prelude (con't); [Roger] Sessions: "Turn O Liebertod"; [Charles] Ives: "William" [sic]
  - Saranac reels 25-27 (9), gss_870; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    NVYAQ
  - Saranac reels 28-30 (10), gss_871; Note on the box reads: "N.B. portions of last take erased accidentally (this safety only)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    NYUAQ
  - Saranac reels 31-33 (11), gss_872; Note on the box is illegible.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    NYVQ
  - Saranac reels 34-36 (12), gss_873; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    Chant; NYVQ
  - Saranac reels 37-38 (13), gss_874; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    37-NYVA
  - Schuman: Esses, gss_156; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
    No slate - "Sukiyaki" (choir, unaccompanied); "Serenata"; "Shimmering"; "Sing-A-Ling" (Ros. solo, tenor solo, clapping)
  - [William] Schuman: "Casey", gss_761; "Casey at the Bat, A Baseball Cantata" by William Schuman; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - [William] Schuman Perceptions, gss_157; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
    No slate: "Equality' (choir, unaccompanied); "To the states" (men's, women's choir; Ros. solo)
  - [William] Schuman: Young Dead Solders, 03/12/1976; gss_751; Note on the box reads: "Rehearsal tape (the rest is illegible)".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Scully (1), gss_601; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Scully (2), gss_602; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Scully (3), gss_603; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Scully (4), gss_604; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Scully (5); Jim Corrons, gss_605; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Scully (6), gss_606; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Scully (7), gss_607; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Scully (8); Jim Corrons (1), gss_608; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Scully (9), gss_609; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Secant - Secular canticle (3), 06/17/1982; gss_852; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - "Shakespeare songs", Shakinsky, 06/17/1982; gss_758; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Shakinsky and secant; Skatunty; Skatsinty (2); Shakespeare and Secular Canticle (2), 06/17/1982; gss_899; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Smith-Brown (1), gss_161; Additional notes by the audio engineer RJH read: "Wordless chorus, unaccompanied, modern music".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 12)
  - Smith - [Earle] Brown, Holly 3, gss_882; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Smith (12), gss_596; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - Smith (13), gss_597; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - Smith (14), gss_598; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 47)
  - Smithanac (2): Cardu - Warble; Hennagin - Meditra, gss_667; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - Smithanac (37), gss_688; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac (38), gss_689; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac (39), gss_690; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (1); Carter; [Ned] Rorem, gss_662; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - Smithanac II (2); Carter; [Ned], (Rose); Rorem (cont.); [John] Boda, gss_663; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - Smithanac II (26), gss_678; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (27), gss_679; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (28), gss_680; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (29), gss_681; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (3), gss_114; Transcribed for the old box front: Rorem con't. End letter, Riley - summer music, label underneath Rem Riley.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 48)
  - Smithanac II (30), gss_682; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (31), gss_683; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (32), gss_684; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (33), gss_685; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (34), gss_686; Note on the box about the stage set up.; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (36), gss_687; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 53)
  - Smithanac II (4): Hearing; Morem, gss_664; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - Smithanac II (5): Hearing; Morem; [Michael] Hennagin: "Dickinson", gss_665; Note on the box reads: "Rorem: Hearing 1/2 of tape. Start of Dickinson duets".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - Smithanac II (6): [Michael] Hennagin duets, gss_666; Note on the box reads: "Plus about 1/3 in from head "Jerusalem".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - Smithanac II Suite-Wheeler (25), gss_029; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 3)
  - Smitten (1), gss_095; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "chorus, unaccompanied".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - Smitten (10), gss_104; Additional note by the audio engineer reads: "Mixed chorus".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Smitten (2), gss_096; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "chorus, unaccompanied".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - Smitten (3), gss_097; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "chorus, unaccompanied, end of tape mangled".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - Smitten (4), gss_098; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Women's chorus, men's chorus at end".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - Smitten (5), gss_099; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Men's chorus, mixed chorus".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - Smitten (6), gss_100; Additional note by the audio engineer RJH reads: "Mixed chorus".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 8)
  - Smitten (7), gss_101; Additional note by the audio engineer reads: "Mixed chorus".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Smitten (8), gss_102; Additional note by the audio engineer reads: "Mixed chorus".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Smitten (9), gss_103; Additional note by the audio engineer reads: "Mixed chorus".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 10)
  - Solikolb Extracts, gss_269; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    Slates: 103; 106; 202; 204: (piano, percussion, xylophone); 301; 303; 306; 404; 407: (piano solo)
  - [Rick] Sowash (1), gss_897; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - [Rick] Sowash (2), gss_915; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 61)
  - Staroz (1), gss_535; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
  - Staroz (2); Bland, Kolb, Cage, Smith, gss_536; Recording of guitar acoustic, percussion, cymbal, soprano performances.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 34)
  - [Igor] Stravinksy: Fl. song; Wolf Songs (1), gss_837; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Igor] Stravinksy: Fl. song; Wolf Songs (2), gss_838; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Igor] Stravinsky II (1), gss_819; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Igor] Stravinsky II (2), gss_820; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Igor] Stravinsky II (3), gss_821; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Igor] Stravinsky II (4); Copernicus II (1), gss_822; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - [Igor] Stravinsky II, gss_818; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 58)
  - Sudden Reif, gss_616; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
  - Suitehartz [sic] (1), gss_721; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - Suitehartz [sic] (2), gss_722; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - Suitehartz [sic] (3), gss_723; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 55)
  - Swickard, gss_266; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    1: Missa Brevis; 2: Psalm (Mixed chorus, soloist)
  - SWK (3 Programs), gss_265; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    (Piano, mixed chorus, Spanish language)
  - Talma (1), gss_282; Additional notes read: "orchestra, chorus, rer."; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: "Louise" comments: 101-113: (orchestra, choir)
  - Talma (2), gss_283; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 201: "Oh, Divine Master"; 202-203: ? (orchestra, soloists, chorus); 204: "See..." (orchestra, soloists, chorus); 206-213: (orchestra, soloists, chorus)
  - Talma (2A), gss_276; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: 201A, 202A: "God"; 203A, 204A, 205A, 206A, 207A, 208A, 209A, 211A: ? (chorus, orchestra); 210A, 212A, 213A, 214A: "May the Lord bless..." (baritone soloist, chorus); 215A: "Be..." (baritone solo, orchestra, chorus)
  - Talma (3); Xmas [Christmas] (1), gss_284; Additional note after Xmas [Christmas] (1) reads: "chorus, rev."; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 301: "First movement " "...dona novis pachem... " (chorus, orchestra); 302-305: ? (chorus, orchestra); 101-105: "Good king Wenceslas" (chorus, orchestra)
  - Talma (3A), gss_277; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    301A: "Be..." (baritone, chorus, orchestra); 302A: "May the Lord bless..." (baritone, chorus, orchestra); 303A: "Men" (baritone, chorus, orchestra); 304A: "Lay me down" (baritone, chorus, orchestra); 306A: ? (baritone, chorus, orchestra); 307A: ? (violists, cello); 308A: "Larry and David" (baritone, chorus, orchestra); 309A: "Shalom" (baritone, chorus, orchestra); 310A, 311A: ? (baritone, chorus, orchestra)
  - Talma (4A), gss_278; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    401A: ? (orchestra, chorus); 402A, 403A, 405B, 406A, 407A, 408A, 409A, 410A, 411A: "Pray for the peace of Jerusalem..." (orchestra, chorus)
  - Talma (5A), gss_279; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: 501A: ? (orchestra, chorus); 502A, 503A, 504A: "Pray for the peace of Jerusalem" (orchestra, chorus); 505A, 506A, 507A, 508A, 509A, 510A, 511A, 512A: ? (orchestra, chorus)
  - Talma (6A), gss_280; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: 601A-613A: (orchestra, chorus)
  - Talma (7A); Xmas [Christmas] (1B), gss_281; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: 701A: "O Lord..." (chorus, unaccomp.); 702A: ? (chorus, unaccomp.); 703A: "And the evening comes..." (chorus, unaccomp.); 704A: "Last" (chorus, unaccomp.); 101B, 102B: "Love" (chorus, unaccomp.); 103B: ? (chorus, unaccomp.); 104B, 105B: "Me thinks..." (chorus, unaccomp.); 106B: "Sing..." (chorus, unaccomp.), 107B: "Me thinks" (chorus, unaccomp.); 108B: "Name" (chorus, unaccomp.)
  - TBC (1): Sanctus; Legend, 05/05/1976; gss_789; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    Sanctus: 101: Complete; 102: FS only; 103: Complete (No Bleep); 104 Stopped Midway; 105: Benedictus to end; 201: FS only; 202: Benedictus (beginning only); 203: Benedictus (to end); 204: FS (his extra bleep); 205: FS (8 measures); 206-207: Complete; Legend: 301-303: FS only; 304: Complete; 305-307: Section I; 308: FS; 309: Section I (slated 308)
  - TBC (2), 05/05/1976; gss_788; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
    401-405: Section II; 406-407: Section III; 408-502: Section IV (Nevertheless); 503-506: Selection IV Insert (Not Die); 507-607: Selection VI FS; 608-609: Selection VII FS
  - TBC (3), 05/05/1976; 05/06/1976; gss_787; Note on the box reads: "N.B. Take 201 front missing on safety".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - TBC (4), 05/06/1976; gss_786; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - TBC (5), 05/06/1976; gss_784; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Thayer (3), gss_271; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
    Slates: 301: (orchestra); 302 (chorus, orchestra, not in English); 303: (fragment chorus, orchestra); 304: (chorus, orchestra); 305: (chorus, orchestra, soloists)
  - Thayer (4), gss_272; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: 401-407: chorus, orchestra, soloists, not English
  - Thayer (5); Xmas [Christmas] (1A), gss_273; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: 501: (cont'd from 272); 502: "Letter J", says G. S. "Amen" (orchestra, chorus, soloists); 503: "From beginning" G. S.; 504: "Amen" (orchestra, chorus, soloists); 505: "First Verse" (soloist, chorus, orchestra) "We 3 kings of Orient are"; 506-507: "Time of wonder...." (chorus, orchestra, baritone, soloist)
  - The Columbia University Glee Club, Feb 1973; gss_621; Programme de la tournee Europeenne in French is inserted in the box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 49)
    1ere partie: Musique d'Europe: Surrexit Christus (giovani Gabrielli); Sehnsucht (Franz Schubert); Le Gibet (Paul Hindemith); Musique d'Amerique - Chants de Charles Ives: Decembre; Serenite; Ils sont la; Chant de Carnaval (Walter Piston); Extraits de Carmina Burana (Carl Orff); 2eme partie: The Brown Notes (Carl Olsen, directeur): When Johnny comes marching home (harmonise par Milt Okun. Chant de marche); La fresnaie; Greensleeves; La bievre (harmonise par Alice Parker); Kumbaya (harmonise par R. Murcell); Sous la tente ce soir; Shenandoah; Ecoute dans le vent (harmonise par R. Murcell); Trois spirituals: Humble (harmonise par Bartholomew); Chaque fois que je sens en moi l'Espirit (harmonise par Stanton); Chansons traditionnelles americaines (harmonisees par AAron Copland): Dense du Batelier; Le Malin; Je me suis achete un chat; A la riviere; Chang-A-Ring-Chaw
  - Trialogue (I and II), Netty Simons, Town Hall Performance tape, 1963; 1968; 05/10/1969; gss_889; Inserted in the box is a letter from Netty Simons to Gregg Smith from July 3, 1973 and a Concert program from May 10, 1969.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    Trialogue (I) (1963) and Trialogue (II) (1968), Netty Simons; Jean Kraft, mezzo; John Ostndorf; John Ostendorf, baritone; Karen Phillips, viola
  - Trismith (1), gss_018; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 2)
  - Trismith (10), gss_657; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Trismith (2), gss_649; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Trismith (2), gss_886; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
  - Trismith (3), gss_650; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Trismith (4), gss_651; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Trismith (5), gss_652; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Trismith (6), gss_653; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Trismith (7), gss_654; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Trismith (8), gss_655; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Trismith (9), gss_656; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 51)
  - Two [?] Madrigals, gss_775; Title is illegible; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 57)
  - Wat Sanc, Wat Clank (16); Koormusiek, 03/18/1974; 03/21/1974; 04/20/1974; gss_590; Label on the box is in Dutch with handwritten description of the recording's content.; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 27:45 (Oversize 47)
    Bay psalta (Dutch) (2 psalms); Consonance by William Billings; Sound Cauhcher [sick] by Gregg Smith; The vision by Dale Gerges [sick]
  - [Anton] Webern (1 and 2): Musical - She Exequen [?], gss_918; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Oversize 61)
  - Xmas [Christmas] (1B); [William] Billings, gss_274; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: 201b: "God sent down an angel..." (chorus, unaccomp.); 203b: discussion "God sent down..." (chorus, unaccomp.); 204b-205b: "To teach us humility..." (chorus, unaccomp.); 206b, 207b, 208b, 209b, 210b: "Me thinks I see..." (chorus, unaccomp.);211b: "Sing..." (chorus, unaccomp.); 212b, 213b: "And Jesus is his name..." (chorus, unaccomp., kidding)
  - Xmas [Christmas] (2), gss_285; Additional note reads: "chorus normal after octet (angles OK)"; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 201-202: "Good king Wenceslas" (orchestra); 203-208: "Angels from the realm of Glory" (chorus, orchestra); 209: "While Shepherds watched their flocks by night" (chorus, orchestra, soloists)
  - Xmas [Christmas] (2A); Talma (1A), gss_275; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 22)
    Slates: 201A: "we three kings" (baritone, tenor, orchestra); 202A, 203A: "Perfect light..." (chorus, baritone, orchestra); 101A, 102A, 103A, 104A, 106A: "Thus said the Lord" (chorus, orchestra); 105A "Two before twelve"(chorus, orchestra)
  - Xmas [Christmas] (3), gss_286; Additional note is illegible; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slate: 301-302: "While Shepherds watched their flocks by night" (chorus, orchestra); 303-304: "Long Ago and Far Away" (chorus, orchestra, soloists, baritone, soprano)
  - Xmas [Christmas] (4), gss_287; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 401: "Long Ago and Far Away" (chorus, orchestra, soprano); 402-403: "Go tell in on the mountain" (orchestra, baritone, chorus)
  - Xmas [Christmas] (5), gss_288; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 501: "Go tell it on the Mountain" (baritone, chorus, orchestra); 502: -504: "What child is this?" (chorus, alto, orchestra); 505: ? (chorus, alto, orchestra, piano)
  - Xmas [Christmas] (6), gss_289; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 601-602: (piano, chorus); 506, 603-605: "O Holy Night" (harp, orchestra, soprano)
  - Xmas [Christmas] (7), gss_290; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 23)
    Slates: 701-704: "O Holy Night" (harp, orchestra, soprano, harp); 705-707: ? (chorus, orchestra)
  - Xmas [Christmas] Ark. dbx (1), gss_259; Program play list is inserted in the box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 21)
  - Xmas [Christmas]; "We Three Kings" (cont.); [Louise] Talma (cont. ), 1984; gss_757; Xmas 1984; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 56)
  - Xmas[Christmas] 1984; [Fred] Thayer, gss_885; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 59)
    "O Holy night"
  - Young Dead Soldiers (1), gss_676; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - Young Dead Soldiers (2), gss_677; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 52)
  - [unknown], blank, Rozrem covered by tape ND; gss_001; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - [unknown], blank, no Label - Interior of Hub says "Manger" #1; gss_003; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)
  - [unknown], blank, no Label - Interior of Hub says "Manger" #2; gss_004; 1/2 inch audio tape (Oversize 1)